ocztechnologyforum.com 2014-12-08

# OCZ Website Privacy Policy

### Online Privacy and Security

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. That's why we at OCZ Storage Solutions believe in an active approach to safeguarding your privacy online. You can interact and remain assured that you are protected by confidentiality, security, and your individual right to change your mind. OCZ provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and Practices, and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online, and how that information is used.

### Confidentiality

In certain areas of this site you may choose to share personal information with us, such as your name, address or even your credit card information. Any personal information you choose to share with us will not be disclosed to anyone outside of OCZ, our related companies, or our business partners who help with this site unless required by law. We will never exchange or sell your personal information to any other company.

### Security

Information in our possession requires a unique password and username to access it. With this password you can edit, delete, or add to information you have shared while visiting our site. Additionally, the information you include in a secure SSL online ordering transaction is encrypted while in transit to us.

### Use of P3P Technology

The Platform for Privacy Preferences (P3P) is a new privacy technology developed by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C). P3P technology can be found within your Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 browser or later and provides you with the ability to make more informed choices about the use of your personal information online.

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 (IE6) was the first browser to support the new privacy standard. With P3P, you can configure your browser to automatically detect if a website collects personally identifiable information, uses that information to create user profiles, or allows visitors to opt-out of the data collection. A P3P-enabled browser has preset options from which you can choose. Or you may customize your setting by answering questions such as, what kinds of data are you willing to share and what types of "cookie" files are you willing to accept. As you surf the Web, the software then determines whether your privacy preferences match a site's data collection practices.

### Information Collection and Use

We will not sell or exchange names or any other information about our online customers. We will not collect, share or sell any information that is not addressed in this statement.

### Types of Information We Collect

**Dynamic Data**. We collect anonymous information about every visit to our site. We do not create individual profiles for visitors, we collect only aggregate data. Our webserver collects click-stream data and HTTP protocol elements in access logs, used solely for the OCZ Website functionality, traffic analysis, research and development. We use IP addresses to track only aggregate information regarding site traffic. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop. We do not collect any personal information via a user's IP address. We use this information only to determine how to make future visits more convenient and productive for our customers. We also collect browser type, access time, and the URL where a user is entering or exiting the site.

**HTTP Cookies.** The P3P-enabled browser places special emphasis on HTTP cookies. A "cookie" is a piece of data which resides on your computer's hard drive to allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. With a P3P-enabled browser you can make selections based on whether you wish to accept various types of cookies such as session (temporary), permanent, within a given domain or outside it (third party), and to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it, with or without a special "P3P compact policy" file. A compact P3P policy describes the attributes of a given cookie. At this time, we do not make use of HTTP cookies.

### How We Use Cookies

Like many websites we use cookies to store and then retrieve small bits of information on your computer when you visit. This information is used to make the site work as you expect it to. It is not personally identifiable to you, but it can be used to give you a more personalised web experience.

Some of the information stored is put there by other companies whose software we have added to the site, and this can also impact your experience of other websites you may visit after leaving ours.

If you continue to use this site without taking action to prevent the storage of this information, you are effectively agreeing to this use.

If you want to learn more about the general uses of cookies, including how to stop them being stored by your computer, please visit Cookiepedia - all about cookies.

Below is a list of the different types of cookies used on this site, and an explanation of what they are used for. If you would like any more information, please get in touch.  

  * **Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are necessary for the website to function. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as logging in or filling in forms.

You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.

  * **Performance Cookies**

These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site.

All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.

_gat   
__utma   
__utmc   
__utmz   
__utmb   
__utmt   
_ga 

  * **Functionality Cookies**

These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalisation. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages.

If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.

__atuvc   
__atuvc   
__atuvc   
__atuvc   
lang   
__atuvc   
__atuvc 

  * **Targeting Cookies**

These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites.

They do not store any personally identifiable information, but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.

dids1437527011   
datr   
tuuid   
pid   
dids87935525   
_te_   
loc   
__adroll   
auth_token   
uit   
APISID   
__ar_v4   
rtn1   
_te_   
dids1582935681   
|  lu   
put_2760   
dids1795147013   
B   
_te_   
xtc   
PREF   
dids879904272   
twll   
__ar_v4   
__ar_v4   
secure_session   
bt2   
dids1277259370   
guest_id   
|  dids168335033   
tuuid   
PUBRETARGET   
__utma   
i   
c   
dids596994156   
_te_   
SID   
_te_   
remember_checked   
CfP   
remember_checked_on   
id   
rpb   
|  KRTBCOOKIE_466   
uid   
bh   
HSID   
ck1   
uvc   
rlas3   
rpx   
um2   
di2   
__ar_v4   
__ar_v4   
khaos   
JEB2   
dt   
  
---|---|---|---  
  * **Other Cookies**

The following cookies are also set by our site, however their purpose has not yet been identified. We are conducting research into these cookies and will update this page as soon as possible.

__atuvs   
__atuvs   
__atuvs   
visitor_id47812   
__atuvs   
visitor_id47812   
visitor_id47812   
pardot   
lpv47812   
__atuvs   
pardot   
__atuvs 

### Policy Evaluation

P3P-compliant browsers will evaluate this privacy policy's "compact policy" whenever it is used with a cookie. Compact policies are a form of a P3P policy which summarize what the privacy policy says about cookies. The actions they will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (i.e., low, medium, medium-high or high). In addition, P3P-compliant browsers will examine whether the cookie's policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context. 

The Compact Policy of OCZ Storage Solutions is considered satisfactory according to the rules defined by the Platform for Privacy Preferences and Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 and later. IE6+ will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the _High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies_ settings.

### Email Links

We use e-mail links throughout the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message (that does not get filtered as spam) and try to reply promptly to everyone. Information in the message is used to respond directly to your comments or questions. We may also file your comments to improve the site and programs, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is not shared with third parties without your explicit permission.

### Your Comments and Suggestions

We always appreciate hearing from you and welcome your comments and emails. But we ask that you exercise good judgment because material we receive will be considered public and non-confidential. Additionally, we reserve the right to use any comments and emails you share without limitation.

### Questions

If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of our site or your experience with our site, or for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of your personal data, you may contact our Site Representative.

### Legal

By visiting this site you are agreeing to the terms as outlined above and in the Terms of Use section.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time.
